<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Emacs for the Mac on Aquamacs Emacs</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/</link><description>Recent content in The Emacs for the Mac on Aquamacs Emacs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aquamacs.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aquamacs 3.5 now available</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/pages/aquamacs-3.5-announce/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/pages/aquamacs-3.5-announce/</guid><description>Aquamacs 3.5 is now available. This is a required update to run on macOS Mojave (macOS 10.14).</description></item><item><title>About Aquamacs</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/about/</guid><description>Aquamacs is a user-friendly build of the powerful Emacs text editor. Aquamacs integrates with the Mac and offers the same comforts that any application on the Mac provides. Yet, it comes with all the ergonomics and extensibility you&amp;#39;ve come to expect from GNU Emacs. Most of the development on Aquamacs since its beginning in 2004 was done by David Reitter, based on GNU Emacs by Richard Stallman and many others.</description></item><item><title>Beta release of Aquamacs 3.6</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/aquamacs-36-beta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/aquamacs-36-beta/</guid><description>The beta release of Aquamacs 3.6 is now available (download).
This release has fixes for many of the reported crashes and other bugs, particularly for crashes on Catalina and Big Sur. Aquamacs now prompts for needed permissions. The Aquamacs app is now fully signed and notarized by Apple. Several of the bundled Emacs Lisp packages have been updated to more recent versions, most notably AUCTeX.
This version also include native support for libxml2 as well as JPEG and SVG images.</description></item><item><title>Development</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/development/</guid><description>Development of the Aquamacs distribution is ongoing. The current focus of development is updating Aquamacs to be based on the most recent release of the main GNU Emacs. I
Mailing lists Interested in Aquamacs? Subscribe and post to our developer mailing list with development questions, comments, and contributions.
The following mailing lists are available:
Aquamacs-devel: for developer discussion (subscription required to post) Emacs on OSX (Archives): for support questions from and interaction with users (subscription required to post) All mailing lists are public and you are welcome to join!</description></item><item><title>Downloads</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/downloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/downloads/</guid><description>Download the latest version of Aquamacs Emacs, as well as older ones.
Current release Based on GNU Emacs 25.3
Aquamacs Emacs 3.6
Older versions Aquamacs Emacs 3.5 (Mac OS 10.12+ Sierra or later) or
Download Version 3.5 for Mac OS El Capitan (only)
Development builds will be back soon.
System requirements for Aquamacs 3.6 Apple MacOS 10.11 (El Capitan) or later Runs on both Intel and Apple Silicon (M1) processors (M1 under Rosetta) Changes in Aquamacs 3.</description></item><item><title>Editing LaTeX with Aquamacs</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/latex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/latex/</guid><description>by Coen de Roover
Most old-school Mac users would never think of using something for their LaTeX editing needs that brings up so many images of command-line hacking as Emacs does. In my personal opinion however, Emacs (with the help of the preview-latex and flyspell extensions) is one of the most advanced LaTeX editing environments available for the Mac. This is especially true for some of the open source projects such as Aquamacs that try to integrate Emacs more into the Mac operating system.</description></item><item><title>Features: Why Use Aquamacs?</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/features/</guid><description>Aquamacs. Finally a GNU Emacs that feels like home. Get all the flexibility and variety of Emacs— and the comfort of the modern graphical user interface that you&amp;#39;re used to from other Mac applications.
Why use Aquamacs instead of a raw GNU Emacs? Why use Aquamacs instead of the stock Carbon or X11 Emacs on the Mac? Here are some features that Aquamacs has to offer on top of all the advantages that come with Emacs:</description></item><item><title>Help &amp; Support</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/help/</guid><description>We&amp;#39;d love to hear from you: your ideas, your experiences, your problems with Aquamacs.
Documentation is readily available—please look there before contacting us.
The Help menu has the Aquamacs manual Check out the Aquamacs Wiki page on the EmacsWiki. You may also use the Aquamacs Wiki to add and tips for customizing and improving Aquamacs. Google: all our mailing lists are indexed. Bug reports
You can send a bug report from within Aquamacs using Help-&amp;gt;Diagnose and Report Bug-&amp;gt;Send Bug report.</description></item><item><title>Reporting problems with Aquamacs</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/reporting-bugs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/reporting-bugs/</guid><description>Reporting problems with Aquamacs Bug reports are sent to the Aquamacs-bugs mailbox using the &amp;#34;Send Bug Report&amp;#34; function in the Aquamacs Help / Diagnose and Report Bug menu. If you have a problem with a particular mode and you&amp;#39;re sure that the bug occurs when using that mode with a plain GNU Emacs (not Aquamacs), then try to get in touch with the developers of that mode. Do not send bug reports to the Emacs on OS X mailing list.</description></item><item><title>Sponsor the Aquamacs Project</title><link>https://aquamacs.org/sponsor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aquamacs.org/sponsor/</guid><description>If you like Aquamacs, consider giving money or your time.
Aquamacs is free software, but producing it takes a lot of time and also some real cash. For many years, a single developer has produced and combined the majority of the code that makes Aquamacs unique compared to a standard Emacs implementation. A number of other volunteers helped by means of bug reporting and making helpful suggestions, through documentation and support, and through contributing special packages.</description></item></channel></rss>